CHARACTERS, PLACES, ORGANIZATIONS AND EVENTS ARE FICTITIOUS
등장인물, 장소, 조직, 사건은 허구입니다.
I confirmed that he entered the police station.
경찰서에 들어간 것을 확인했습니다.
If he obstructed justice and assaulted a police officer,
만약 그가 정의를 방해 하고 경찰을 폭행했다면,
it won't be simple.
간단하지 않을 것입니다.
Seek more information.
더 많은 정보를 찾아보세요.
Yes, boss.
예 보스.
And discover the suspicions that motivated Hwang Mingoo.
그리고 황민구에게 동기를 부여한 의혹을 찾아보세요 .
Yes sir.
알겠습니다.
No...
아니요...
Apparently, you were once an athlete.
분명히 당신은 한때 운동선수였습니다.
But today he is a marginal.
그러나 오늘날 그는 한계가 있습니다.
If you cross the line with the police,
경찰과 선을 넘으면
you could end up dead.
당신은 죽을 수도 있습니다.
You laughed?
웃었어요?
Are the South Korean police a joke to you?
한국 경찰이 농담인가요?
I already know.
나는 이미 알고 있다.
I'll take off the badge. How about solving it by beating it up?
뱃지를 떼겠습니다. 두들겨 패서 해결해 보는 건 어떨까요?
-Calm down, sir. -Come up, son of a bitch!
- 진정하세요, 선생님. -어서 와, 개자식아!
Come on, bastard!
어서, 개자식!
-Let me go. -Calm down, sir.
- 놔주세요. - 진정하세요, 선생님.
Get rid of that arrogance.
그 오만함을 없애십시오.
Or do you want to go straight to jail?
아니면 바로 감옥에 가고 싶나요?
As you can see,
보시다시피,
I came to surrender.
항복하러 왔습니다.
Skirt. And even?
치마. 그리고 심지어?
If you came to surrender,
항복하러 왔다면,
lift your head and list all your crimes.
고개를 들고 모든 범죄를 나열하십시오.
I lost control and crossed the line
통제력을 잃고 선을 넘어버렸어
when attacking a public servant.
공무원을 공격할 때
Sorry.
죄송합니다.
I told you to list the crimes, not apologize, damn it.
사과하지 말고 죄목을 나열하라고 했잖아 , 젠장.
I accept any punishment.
나는 어떤 처벌도 받아들입니다.
Enough chit-chat.
충분한 잡담.
Who were those people in the hotel room?
호텔 방에 있던 사람들은 누구였나요 ?
Listen here.
여기 들어보세요.
I'm not interested in fucking a nobody like you, okay?
난 너 같은 사람이랑 섹스하는 것엔 관심 없어 , 알았지?
Who were those sons of bitches?
그 개자식들은 누구였나요?
Those who left the hotel room with Jung Gicheul.
정기철과 함께 호텔방을 떠난 이들 .
Who is this?
누구세요?
Who are these fuckers?
이 새끼들은 누구야?
-I don't know. -Then...
-모르겠습니다. -그 다음에...
Don't try to take the blame. Just tell me the truth.
책임을 지려고 하지 마십시오. 그냥 진실을 말해주세요.
Who are they?
그들은 누구입니까?
I'm a fucking nobody, so I don't know anything.
저는 아무것도 모르는 사람 이라 아무것도 모릅니다.
I just know...
그냥 알아요...
that they invest in my boss.
그들이 내 상사에게 투자한다는 것입니다.
Just that.
바로 그거야.
As if! Who invests in a criminal?
마치! 누가 범죄자에게 투자합니까?
And why did investors run away?
그리고 투자자들은 왜 도망갔는가?
Just look...
그냥 봐...
It would be strange not to run away
도망치지 않는 게 이상할 텐데
of a police officer who arrives screaming like a crazy person.
미친 사람처럼 비명을 지르며 도착한 경찰관의 모습 .
What the fuck did you say?
도대체 무슨 말을 했어?
Repeat what you said.
당신이 말한 것을 반복하십시오.
It seems that you were also an athlete.
당신도 운동선수였던 것 같습니다.
Truth be told. Who was once an athlete,
진실을 말하십시오. 한때 운동선수였던 사람,
You just become a criminal or a police officer, right?
그냥 범죄자나 경찰이 되는 거죠?
AND?
그리고?
We are practically the same.
우리는 사실상 동일합니다.
Just had a little more luck
조금 더 운이 좋았을 뿐입니다
for holding this position today.
오늘 이 자리를 지켜주셔서.
Police officer, just look at one thing.
경찰관님, 하나만 보세요.
He's acting like a criminal.
그는 범죄자처럼 행동하고 있습니다.
Damn!
젠장!
Don't you feel ashamed, you worm?
부끄럽지 않니, 벌레야?
Seriously, sir. Let me go!
진심입니다. 날 보내줘!
It's done, bastard!
다 됐다, 개자식아!
Son of a bitch!
개자식!
Come here, son of a bitch!
이리 오세요, 개자식아!
-Sir. -Fucking hell!
-선생님. -젠장!
-Take it here!
- 여기로 가져가세요!
Son of a bitch!
개자식!
Stop, sir.
그만하세요.
-Stop. -Let me go!
-멈추다. - 놔줘!
Stupid son of a bitch!
멍청한 개자식아!
Damned hell!
빌어먹을 지옥!
Let go of me, idiot!
날 놔, 바보야!
Take it here.
여기로 가져가세요.
You think you can escape my punches, you fucker?
내 펀치를 피할 수 있을 것 같아 ?
Fucking scoundrel!
빌어먹을 악당!
Do you think you'll escape my punches, scoundrel?
내 주먹을 피할 수 있을 것 같아 , 악당?
How dare you?
어떻게 감히?
Fucking scoundrel!
빌어먹을 악당!
-How dare you? -I already asked you to stop!
- 어떻게 감히요? -이미 그만하라고 했어요!
Let go of me, idiot!
날 놔, 바보야!
THE WORST OF EVIL
최악의 악
Very good. Let's continue.
매우 좋은. 계속합시다.
Then...
그 다음에...
Who were those?
그 사람들은 누구였나요?
Fuck, I don't know.
젠장, 모르겠어요.
Holy shit, you piece of shit!
이런 젠장, 이 빌어먹을 놈아!
Do you still think I'm joking?
아직도 내가 농담하고 있다고 생각하시나요?
What? Are you going to hit me again?
무엇? 또 때릴 건가요?
You can hit.
칠 수 있습니다.
Kill me already, asshole.
날 벌써 죽여라, 이 새끼야.
It can leave. Die, motherfucker.
떠날 수 있습니다. 죽어라 개자식아.
What's going on here?
여기서 무슨 일이 일어나고 있는 걸까요?
Is this kind of thing common in the Gangnam Police Station?
강남경찰서에 이런 일이 흔한가요 ?
No sir.
아닙니다.
No way.
안 돼요.
Sir,
선생님,
May I ask the reason for your surprise visit?
깜짝 방문 이유를 물어봐도 될까요 ?
I came to bring information about a homicide case.
살인 사건에 대한 정보를 가지고 왔습니다 .
I heard they were in the middle of an investigation.
조사를 진행 중이라고 들었습니다 .
Yes sir. Involves a missing drug dealer
알겠습니다. 실종된 마약상이 연루되어 있습니다.
known as Manager Cho.
조 매니저로 알려져 있다.
Maybe it's the same case.
어쩌면 같은 경우 일 수도 있습니다.
But I can't help a police officer who commits violence.
하지만 폭력을 행사하는 경찰관을 도울 수는 없습니다 .
I need to report the assault that just happened, right?
방금 일어난 폭행 사건을 신고해야 겠죠 ?
Please sir.
부탁드립니다 선생님.
We are sorry for what happened.
무슨 일이 일어났는지 유감스럽게 생각합니다.
I will take strict measures to discipline my officers.
나는 직원들을 징계하기 위해 엄격한 조치를 취할 것입니다.
I ask you to let it go just this once.
이번 한 번만 놔두시기 바랍니다.
He heard?
그는 들었다?
I'll be more careful.
좀 더 조심하겠습니다.
Take it.
가져.
What the hell...
도대체 무슨...
What it was?
그게 뭐였지?
They asked me to sign something saying I won't sue them.
그들은 나에게 고소하지 않겠다는 내용의 서명을 해달라고 요청했습니다 .
They said they would release me if I forgot
잊어버리면 풀어준다고 하더군요
the aggression.
침략.
Listen...
듣다...
Say.
말하다.
You know everything, right?
당신은 다 알고 있죠?
What?
무엇?
You saw everything at the hotel.
호텔에서 다 봤어요.
What does the boss do?
사장은 무슨 일을 하나요?
What's the deal with China?
중국과 무슨 관계가 있나요?
Why the fuck did he take you instead of me?
도대체 왜 나 대신 널 데려간 거지?
It's related to drugs.
마약과 관련이 있습니다.
My father is an addict, you know.
우리 아버지는 중독자예요.
So it's an area that I dominate.
그래서 제가 지배하는 영역이에요.
I suspected this shit.
나는 이것을 의심했다.
Only the three heads are involved.
머리 세 개만 관련됩니다.
Let's join them, Boss Seo.
함께 합시다, 서보스.
You wanted to get rich.
당신은 부자가 되고 싶었어요.
I'll only earn big if they let me participate.
참여를 허락해 주어야만 큰 돈을 벌 수 있습니다 .
We need to participate no matter what.
우리는 무슨 일이 있어도 참여해야 합니다.
If you don't have space,
공간이 없다면,
we take someone out.
우리는 누군가를 데리고 나갑니다.
Are you serious?
진심인가요?
You deserve to be part of this.
당신은 이것의 일부가 될 자격이 있습니다.
Nobody cares more than you.
아무도 당신보다 더 관심이 없습니다.
Seriously, it's a complete injustice.
엄밀히 말하면 그것은 완전한 불의입니다.
You deserve to get rich.
당신은 부자가 될 자격이 있습니다.
Tome.
나에게.
Good job.
잘했어요.
Thanks.
감사해요.
He was very lucky, really.
그는 정말 운이 좋았습니다.
He was being beaten by Hwang Mingoo,
황민구에게 구타당하고 있었는데,
and the chief prosecutor showed up just in time.
그리고 때마침 수석검사가 나타났다.
Does your police friend
당신의 경찰 친구는
Did you touch him?
그 사람을 만졌나요?
Were you upset because Seungho was released?
승호가 풀려서 속상하셨나요 ?
There were plainclothes police officers inside that hotel.
그 호텔 안에는 사복경찰이 있었어요 .
What are you talking about?
무슨 얘기를 하는 건가요?
Did you happen to see it?
우연히 보셨나요?
It was just my intuition.
그것은 단지 내 직감이었습니다.
Did you have that intuition?
그런 직감이 있었나요?
Your intuition always gets it right.
당신의 직관은 항상 옳습니다.
Why didn't you unmask the police officer?
왜 경찰관의 가면을 벗기지 않았나요?
I can't come up and ask, "Are you a police officer?"
다가가서 "당신은 경찰이세요?"라고 물어볼 수는 없습니다.
You're right.
네가 옳아.
You can notice their presence.
그들의 존재를 알 수 있습니다.
Wherever you go, there are always some public servants.
어딜가든 공무원은 꼭 있습니다.
Plainclothes police, prosecutor
사복 경찰, 검사
and that friend of yours.
그리고 그 친구.
The police officer from the Security Division.
보안과 소속 경찰관.
Jungbae.
정배.
Yes sir.
알겠습니다.
What are your suspicions?
당신의 의심은 무엇입니까?
Well, then...
그럼...
No one gets away with attacking a police officer.
경찰을 공격하고도 도망갈 수 있는 사람은 없습니다 .
So the cops are protecting Seungho?
그럼 경찰이 승호를 보호하고 있는 걸까요?
This is certainly not the case,
이것은 확실히 사실이 아닙니다.
but there is something strange.
그런데 뭔가 이상한 게 있어요.
Seungho went there in your place.
승호가 너 대신 갔어.
Leave it there. Let's enjoy the drink.
거기에 두십시오. 음료를 즐기자.
-Jungbae. -May I help?
-정배. -제가 도와 드릴까요?
There are several inconsistencies in this month's accounting.
이번 달 회계에는 몇 가지 불일치가 있습니다 .
Need to tidy up.
정리가 필요합니다.
Sure, boss. It can leave.
물론이죠, 보스. 떠날 수 있습니다.
Jungbae takes care of the company's accounting.
정배는 회사의 회계업무를 담당하고 있습니다 .
He is very meticulous. I hope he understands.
그는 매우 꼼꼼합니다. 그가 이해해주기를 바랍니다.
Boss,
사장,
What did you decide with the Chinese?
중국인과 무엇을 결정 했습니까?
We are still at an impasse.
우리는 여전히 막다른 골목에 있습니다.
What if you talked to them?
그들과 이야기를 나누면 어떨까요?
Forgiveness?
용서?
The Chinese woman was interested in you.
그 중국 여자가 당신에게 관심이 있었어요.
Why don't you go out and talk?
나가서 얘기해 보는 게 어때?
Like this?
이와 같이?
Seungho is smart and solves things,
승호는 똑똑하고 문제도 잘 해결하고,
but he is still a newbie.
하지만 그는 아직 초보자입니다.
Especially for something of this relevance.
특히 이와 관련된 내용에 대해서는 더욱 그렇습니다.
I think this role is yours.
이 역할은 당신의 것이라고 생각합니다.
The conversation only flows as equals.
대화는 평등하게 흘러갑니다.
These ingrates from China and Japan forget
중국과 일본의 이 배은망덕한 사람들은 잊어버린다
who only became rich because of me.
나 때문에 부자가 된 사람.
They despised me and insulted me.
그들은 나를 멸시하고 모욕했습니다.
They're sons of bitches.
개자식들이야.
I'll handle it, boss.
제가 처리하겠습니다, 보스.
I can fix these scoundrels
내가 이 악당들을 고칠 수 있어
who insulted you.
누가 당신을 모욕했는지.
Let's talk about this later,
이에 대해서는 나중에 얘기하자.
when Jungbae is here.
정배가 왔을 때.
Okay, let's drink.
알았어, 마시자.
Kwon Seungho did very well.
권승호 정말 잘했어요.
And whether you're with a drug dealer or not.
그리고 당신이 마약상과 함께 있든 없든 상관없습니다.
There's no way to help.
도와드릴 방법이 없습니다.
His Japanese godfather thinks he is the king himself.
그의 일본인 대부는 자신이 왕이라고 생각합니다.
Will you disobey?
불순종할 것인가?
So our agreement came to an end.
그래서 우리의 계약은 끝났습니다.
Hello?
안녕하세요?
Oi, Euijeong.
어이, 의정.
LEE AND BODYGUARDS
리와 보디가드
I informed the Chinese police about the fake passports.
나는 위조 여권에 대해 중국 경찰에 알렸다 .
They will start an investigation too.
그들도 조사를 시작할 것이다.
We are almost there.
우리는 거의 다 왔습니다.
We discovered the intentions of the Chinese and the Japanese.
우리는 중국인과 일본인의 의도를 알아냈습니다 .
We already know what they plan.
우리는 그들이 무엇을 계획하는지 이미 알고 있습니다.
Why don't we arrest them soon?
빨리 체포하는 게 어때요?
We can not do that.
우리는 그렇게 할 수 없습니다.
And if this Miss. Lee close the drug factory?
그리고 만약 이씨가 마약공장을 폐쇄한다면?
What if the Japanese insist that they only bought fake glasses and watches?
일본인이 가짜 안경과 시계만 샀다고 주장한다면 어떻게 될까요?
In that case, our only option would be to accuse Jung Gicheul of murder.
그렇다면 우리가 할 수 있는 유일한 선택은 정기철을 살인죄로 고발하는 것뿐이다.
We just need one more thing.
한 가지만 더 필요합니다.
Catch them red-handed at the time of negotiation.
협상할 때 적발해서 잡아라 .
The problem is that their agreement is hanging by a thread.
문제는 이들의 합의가 난항을 겪고 있다는 점이다.
We can't let it break. We need them to negotiate again.
우리는 그것이 깨지도록 놔둘 수 없습니다. 우리는 그들이 다시 협상해야 합니다.
Drug...
의약품...
All good. I'll talk to the Chinese woman.
문제 없다. 중국 여자한테 얘기해 볼게요.
I want them to fix Choi Jungbae.
최정배를 고쳐줬으면 좋겠다.
He's the one who suspects me the most.
나를 가장 의심하는 사람은 바로 그 사람이다.
I have no idea how he will react.
나는 그가 어떻게 반응할지 전혀 모른다.
Let's get him away from Jung Gicheul as quickly as possible.
최대한 빨리 정기철에게서 그를 떼어내자 .
I noticed you're worried.
나는 당신이 걱정하고 있다는 것을 알아차렸습니다.
Can you notice?
눈치챌 수 있나요?
In difficult times, you were always quiet.
어려운 시기에도 당신은 늘 조용했습니다.
Whatever it is,
그것이 무엇이든,
I know it will turn around.
나는 그것이 바뀔 것이라는 것을 알고 있습니다.
As he always did.
그가 늘 그랬듯이.
In the old days, we would meet at night
옛날엔 밤에 만나곤 했어
and talked about everything. Remember?
그리고 모든 것에 대해 이야기했습니다. 기억하다?
I remember. And truth.
기억해. 그리고 진실.
I know by chance...
우연히 알아요...
need help, let me know.
도움이 필요하면 알려주세요.
Why?
왜?
As?
처럼?
Do you want to help me?
나를 도와주고 싶나요?
You helped...
당신은 도움이되었습니다 ...
Seungho too?
승호도요?
Like this?
이와 같이?
Anything.
아무것.
Talking to you makes me feel good.
당신과 이야기하면 기분이 좋아집니다.
Euijeong.
의정.
How do you cope
당신은 어떻게 대처합니까?
Missing your mother?
어머니가 그리워요?
I don't read.
나는 읽지 않는다.
I let the sadness take over.
나는 슬픔이 이어지도록 내버려 두었습니다.
It was nice talking to you. Be careful on the way back.
당신과 이야기해서 좋았습니다. 돌아오는 길에 조심하세요.
Goodnight.
안녕히 주무세요.
Hey.
여기요.
-Have you eaten yet? -Good...
-아직 식사하셨나요? -좋은...
Not yet.
아직 아님.
For you ma'am.
당신을 위해 부인.
Our!
우리의!
Thanks for the food.
음식 주셔서 감사합니다.
Very good.
매우 좋은.
Why don't you go to church anymore?
더 이상 교회에 가지 않겠습니까?
Ashamed of me?
내가 부끄러워요?
Don't say that.
그렇게 말하지 마세요.
What kind of mother is ashamed of her son?
어떤 엄마가 아들을 부끄러워합니까?
Can you do me a favor?
부탁 하나만 들어줄 수 있나요?
TAKE AWAY
테이크아웃
How can I help you?
어떻게 도와 드릴까요?
Hello?
안녕하세요?
Hey.
여기요.
Say.
말하다.
It's Kwon Seungho.
권승호입니다.
We saw each other that day at the hotel.
그날 우리는 호텔에서 만났습니다.
Clear! So you managed to get away with it?
분명한! 그래서 그 일을 피해 도망칠 수 있었나요?
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
Do you think I hid a damn bomb?
내가 폭탄을 숨겼다고 생각하시나요?
I remembered. He doesn't speak Korean.
나는 기억했다. 그 사람은 한국어를 못해요.
Damn, so that's how you got away with it?
젠장, 그래서 그걸로 도망친 거야?
Was a beating enough to solve it?
구타만으로도 해결될 정도였나요?
No.
아니요.
Take good care of her, you hear?
그 사람을 잘 돌봐주세요, 아시죠?
So this bastard speaks Korean.
그럼 이 새끼는 한국말을 하는군요.
Are you coming from the hotel?
호텔에서 오시나요?
Maybe yes maybe no.
어쩌면 예 어쩌면 아니오.
I understood.
나는 이해했다.
Where do you want to go?
어디로 가고 싶나요?
Somewhere with lots of land and houses.
땅과 집이 많은 곳.
Who is it?
누구입니까?
I came to request your services.
나는 당신의 서비스를 요청하기 위해 왔습니다.
We are closed.
문 닫았습니다.
You know me.
당신은 나를 알고 있습니다.
I work with Jung Gicheul.
정기철과 함께 일해요.
What do you want?
당신은 무엇을 원합니까?
I didn't come to ask for anything complicated.
복잡한 걸 달라고 온 게 아닙니다.
You know that woman my boss asked for information from?
내 상사가 정보를 요청한 여자를 아시나요 ?
I just wanted to know
나는 그냥 알고 싶었어
a little more about her.
그녀에 대해 조금 더.
In what sense?
어떤 의미에서?
A newbie named Kwon Seungho arrived.
권승호라는 신인이 왔다.
He says he went to the same school as Yu Euijeong.
유의정과 같은 학교를 다녔다고 한다 .
I want to know if it's true.
그것이 사실인지 알고 싶습니다.
I also need to know if she really lived in Wonju.
그 사람이 정말 원주에 살았는지 도 알고 싶어요 .
If she lived there, was she Kwon Seungho's neighbor?
거기 살았다면 권승호의 이웃이었을까?
I noticed you didn't like my order.
나는 당신이 내 주문을 좋아하지 않는다는 것을 알았습니다.
If you confirm the information, I will pay triple.
정보 확인하시면 3배로 지불하겠습니다.
Hello? It's Cheon speaking.
안녕하세요? 천씨입니다.
One of your guys came here.
너희 친구 중 한 명이 여기 왔어.
Choi Jungbae?
최정배?
Yes, that's him.
네, 그 사람이에요.
Did you mention the other accounting book?
다른 회계서를 언급했나요?
I only do what you say.
나는 당신이 말한 대로만 할 뿐입니다.
I did not say anything.
나는 아무 말 안했어.
Your job is to be a tour guide.
당신의 직업은 여행 가이드입니다.
Aren't you going to explain things to me?
나한테 이것저것 설명해주지 않을 거야?
Well, then...
그럼...
That is...
그건...
a roofed house from the Joseon Dynasty.
조선시대 지붕이 있는 집.
I understood.
나는 이해했다.
And those fish...
그리고 저 물고기...
Are carps from the Joseon Dynasty?
잉어는 조선시대인가요?
It's a lake from the Joseon Dynasty, so...
조선시대 호수라서...
Didn't you say you wanted to look at real estate?
부동산을 보고 싶다고 하지 않았나요 ?
Houses with old roofs are also real estate.
오래된 지붕이 있는 집도 부동산입니다.
Didn't stop here just to find out
단지 알아보기 위해 여기서 멈추지 않았습니다
if someone followed us?
누군가 우리를 따라왔다면?
I thought you only had muscles,
근육만 있는줄 알았는데
but it has a brain too.
하지만 뇌도 있어요.
Have you finished the inspection?
검사는 끝났나요?
How about we eat something nice?
우리 맛있는 거 먹는 게 어때요?
Something very tasty and typical.
매우 맛있고 전형적인 것.
Seungho, you don't look like a gangster.
승호 씨, 당신은 깡패처럼 보이지 않아요.
Looks more like a soldier.
좀 더 군인같네요.
Don't see me as a gangster.
나를 갱스터로 보지 마세요.
see me
나를 봐
as an aspiring entrepreneur.
야심 찬 기업가로서.
May I ask...
내가 요청할 수 있습니다...
What part of China are you from?
당신은 중국 어느 지역 출신인가요?
Guess.
추측하다.
Shanghai?
상하이?
Beijing?
베이징?
Then...
그 다음에...
When we see each other again,
우리가 다시 만날 때,
I will be sharp in China's geography.
나는 중국의 지리를 예리하게 다룰 것입니다.
Why are you so loyal to Mr. Jung
왜 그렇게 정씨에게 충성하는 걸까요?
to the point of risking your life?
목숨을 걸 정도로?
Clear.
분명한.
I don't know.
모르겠습니다.
Simply...
간단히...
it comes from within.
그것은 내부에서 나옵니다.
Inside?
내부에?
-Yes. -I thought...
-예. -생각했는데...
that was in exchange for some property or asset.
그것은 어떤 재산이나 자산을 대가로 받은 것이었습니다.
No.
아니요.
I really admire him
나는 그를 정말로 존경한다
and I like him.
그리고 나는 그를 좋아합니다.
And my body follows my heart.
그리고 내 몸은 내 마음을 따릅니다.
What a romantic guy!
정말 낭만적인 사람이에요!
This is bad?
이게 나쁜거야?
No, on the contrary. I just found it curious.
아니요, 그 반대입니다. 그냥 궁금해서 봤습니다.
It's unusual.
특이한데요.
Then,
그 다음에,
I still don't know your name.
나는 아직도 당신의 이름을 모릅니다.
Lee Haeryun.
이해련.
What form of treatment should I use?
어떤 형태의 치료를 사용해야 합니까?
You can call me whatever you want.
당신이 원하는 대로 저를 부르시면 됩니다.
Haeryun,
해륜,
Will you continue to negotiate with Mr. Jung?
정씨와 계속 협상을 하시겠습니까?
The accident that happened will never happen again.
일어난 사고는 다시는 일어나지 않을 것입니다.
I will be by Mr. Jung's side to ensure it doesn't happen again.
다시는 이런 일이 발생하지 않도록 정씨 곁에서 있겠습니다 .
Can bring.
가져올 수 있습니다.
We have some Korean informants who work nights.
밤에 일하는 한국인 정보원도 있어요 .
They told us where to buy meth.
그들은 우리에게 필로폰 구입처를 알려주었습니다.
If it sinks, it's bad.
가라 앉으면 나쁘다.
If it bubbles, it is of high quality.
거품이 나면 고품질입니다.
The quality of this one is excellent.
이것의 품질이 우수합니다.
Only we offer this quality.
오직 우리만이 이 품질을 제공합니다.
And what does that mean?
그리고 그것은 무엇을 의미합니까?
Here is a typical dish.
다음은 전형적인 요리입니다.
Try it.
시도 해봐.
Mr. Jung embezzled our products,
정씨가 당사 제품을 횡령하여
that should arrive in Japan,
일본에 도착해야 하는데,
to sell them here in South Korea.
여기 한국에서 팔려고요.
How to negotiate with someone who doesn't inspire trust?
신뢰를 얻지 못하는 사람과 협상하는 방법은 무엇입니까 ?
My apologies.
사과드립니다.
I don't know how my boss works.
우리 상사가 어떻게 일하는지 모르겠어요.
And that?
그리고 그거?
Don't you have anything else to say?
더 할 말 없으세요?
No suggestions?
제안사항이 없나요?
Wait, I have a proposal.
잠깐만요, 제안이 있어요.
If you don't trust my boss...
내 상사를 믿지 못한다면...
you can trust me.
당신은 나를 믿을 수 있습니다.
I'll take it to Japan,
일본으로 가져갈게요
in my boss's place.
내 상사의 자리에서.
Give me a chance.
나에게 기회를주세요.
So you're going to betray Mr. Jung?
그럼 정씨를 배신하겠다는 겁니까?
I will not betray you.
나는 당신을 배신하지 않을 것입니다.
I will ask his permission
나는 그 사람에게 허락을 구할 것이다
to officially participate in the operation.
공식적으로 작전에 참여합니다.
If I help you make a profit,
내가 당신이 이익을 얻을 수 있도록 도와준다면,
there is no reason for him to object.
그가 반대할 이유가 없습니다.
However,
하지만,
what difference does it make to me
그것이 나에게 어떤 차이를 가져오는가
for you to be the intermediary?
당신이 중재자가 되어주겠어요?
The difference is that...
차이점은...
if we work together,
우리가 함께 일하면,
will spend more time with me.
나와 더 많은 시간을 보낼 것입니다.
Seung Ho.
승호
When it comes to work,
일할 때,
What do you think is worth more?
무엇이 더 가치 있다고 생각하시나요?
The heart or the money?
마음인가, 돈인가?
Gicheul diverts products that go to Japan.
기철은 일본으로 가는 제품을 우회합니다.
The Chinese discovered that it sells here.
중국인은 그것이 여기에서 판매된다는 것을 발견했습니다.
Cum! The agreement with the Chinese company could end up going down the drain.
정액! 중국 기업과의 합의가 물거품이 될 수도 있다.
We need to act.
우리는 행동해야 합니다.
Let's stop these drugs from being sold here.
여기서는 이 약이 판매되는 것을 중단합시다 .
When we resolve this,
우리가 이 문제를 해결하면,
I will find a way to convince the Chinese.
중국인을 설득할 방법을 찾겠습니다.
They said they sell the drug at Tae-ho Rock Cafe.
태호락카페에서 약을 판다고 하더군요 .
Let's set up bait for Choi Jungbae
최정배를 위한 미끼를 마련하자
and deliver us from it.
그리고 우리를 그것에서 구원해 주십시오.
Let's go!
갑시다!
Hey, how are you?
안녕하세요?
Okay, let's do it.
좋아, 해보자.
Shouldn't they dress better here? What outfit is that?
여기서는 옷을 더 잘 입어야 하지 않나요? 그거 무슨 옷이에요?
Good evening, sir.
좋은 밤입니다.
OK let's go.
확인 가자.
Let's go.
갑시다.
NARCOTICS DIVISION
마약과
As for Tae-ho Rock Cafe...
태호락카페라면...
I'm fucking talking to you.
지금 너랑 얘기하는 중이야.
Right.
오른쪽.
Rumor has it that there's a new drug there.
거기에 새로운 약이 있다는 소문이 있어요.
-I understood. -"Gangnam Crystal."
-이해했어요. -'강남 크리스탈'.
-And you are the owner of the nightclub. -I am.
- 그리고 당신은 나이트클럽의 주인입니다. -그래요.
Then you must know something.
그렇다면 당신은 뭔가를 알아야합니다.
Can I have a cigarette?
담배 좀 피워도 될까요?
Do not know?
모른다?
Cum...
정액...
What is this?
이게 뭔가요?
Are many.
많습니다.
You are a very curious guy.
당신은 매우 호기심이 많은 사람입니다.
-It is written in Chinese. -Chinese?
- 중국어로 쓰여 있어요. -중국인?
Bring a Chinese dictionary.
중국어 사전을 가져오세요.
Do you want some time to reflect alone?
혼자 반성의 시간을 갖고 싶으신가요?
Are we supposed to wait outside?
우리 밖에서 기다려야 하나요?
Of course, no problem. We leave.
물론 문제 없습니다. 우리는 떠난다.
Get back to work!
다시 일하세요!
Feel free to read everything and think.
모든 것을 자유롭게 읽고 생각하십시오.
The Chinese woman doesn't stop talking about trust.
중국 여자는 신뢰에 대한 이야기를 멈추지 않습니다 .
They are considering
그들은 고려하고 있다
ask the Japanese to cancel the operation.
일본에 작전 취소를 요청하세요.
Boss,
사장,
Instead of standing still, we...
가만히 있는 것보다 우리는...
Don't let them open their mouths.
그들이 입을 열지 못하게 하세요.
Gicheul, Jungbae was arrested.
기철, 정배가 체포됐다.
-What? -And now?
-무엇? -그리고 지금?
Damn cops!
빌어먹을 경찰들!
Circling!
돌고 있어요!
Get out of the way.
비켜가세요.
Get out of here.
여기서 나가.
Get down from there!
거기서 내려오세요!
Turn off the music.
음악을 끄십시오.
-Let's get them out there. -Group everyone on one side!
-그들을 밖으로 내보내자. -모두 한 쪽으로 모여주세요!
-Fast! -Get down from there!
-빠른! -거기서 내려와!
This is the police.
여기는 경찰이에요.
Like this?
이와 같이?
If you cooperate, we won't be long.
협조해 주시면 오래 걸리지 않을 거예요.
Stop now!
지금 멈춰!
Tramp, don't do anything.
트램프, 아무것도 하지 마세요.
Turn around and stand still.
돌아 서서 가만히 서십시오.
Get him!
그를 잡아!
Come here!
이리 오세요!
-Hold on tight. -Let me go!
-꽉 잡아. - 놔줘!
What the fuck are you doing?
도대체 뭐하는 거야?
Well, what do you think?
글쎄, 어떻게 생각하세요?
Treasure hunt.
보물 찾기.
Here it is.
여기있어.
Shit.
똥.
Cum...
정액...
Officer Choi.
최 과장.
Man, I'm so envious of these famous people's lives.
아, 이런 유명한 사람들의 삶이 너무 부러워요 .
Damn...
젠장...
Excuse me sir.
실례합니다.
Chord.
현.
What...
무엇...
What?
무엇?
We're from the police.
우리는 경찰 출신이에요.
You logo!
당신은 로고!
-How dare you? -Cum!
- 어떻게 감히요? -쿰!
-What? -Get your hands off me.
-무엇? -나한테서 손 떼세요.
I already told you to get out of the way.
이미 비켜가라고 말했잖아요.
Holy shit!
젠장!
-Come on, come on. -Son of a bitch.
-어서, 어서. -개자식.
Ignore people.
사람을 무시하세요.
Continue thinking.
계속 생각해보세요.
-What? -Collect your urine.
-무엇? -소변을 모아보세요.
Who told you about me?
누가 나에 대해 말했습니까?
Who was the idiot that told on me?
나한테 그런 말을 한 바보가 누구였지?
In that other room,
그 다른 방에서는,
is the owner of Tae-ho Rock Cafe, Choi Jungbae.
태호락카페의 오너 최정배입니다.
You know who you are.
넌 네가 누구인지 안다.
He also attended Yeoksam High School, right?
그 사람 역삼고등학교 도 다녔죠 ?
Shit!
똥!
Sir, we're done.
선생님, 끝났습니다.
If you're not going to talk, you'd better go home and rest.
말 안 할 거면 집에 가서 쉬는 게 좋을 것 같아요.
What it was?
그게 뭐였지?
You're not a suspect, you're just a witness.
당신은 용의자가 아닙니다. 당신은 단지 증인일 뿐입니다.
If you don't have anything to say, you can go.
할말 없으시면 가셔도 됩니다.
-Give me a cigarette. -There is no more.
- 담배 한 대 주세요. -더 이상은 없습니다.
Go buy. You're rich.
가서 사세요. 당신은 부자입니다.
What did you tell the police?
경찰에 뭐라고 말했어요?
What could I have said?
내가 무슨 말을 할 수 있었을까?
They were the ones who brought it up.
그 문제를 제기한 것은 바로 그들이었습니다.
They talked about rumors of meth sales
그들은 마약 판매에 관한 소문에 대해 이야기했습니다.
and they asked me about it.
그리고 그들은 나에게 그것에 대해 물었습니다.
And there?
거기?
I did not say anything.
나는 아무 말 안했어.
Then they ransacked the nightclub.
그런 다음 그들은 나이트클럽을 약탈했습니다.
So that means...
그러니까 그 말은...
that I am to blame for this?
내가 이 일에 책임이 있다고?
Get out! I need to talk to him.
나가세요! 그 사람과 얘기 좀 해야 해요.
What the hell is that?
도대체 무슨 일이 있다는 것입니다?
Gicheul!
기철!
-Choi Jungbae, bastard! -What is it?
-최정배 새끼야! -이게 뭐죠?
How dare you tell on me?
어떻게 감히 나한테 말을 해?
Son of a bitch!
개자식!
How dare you fuck up the life of a former colleague, you asshole?
어떻게 감히 전 동료의 인생을 망칠 수 있겠는가 , 이 멍청한 놈아?
What bullshit is this? I didn't tell on anyone, idiot!
이게 무슨 헛소리야? 난 아무한테도 말하지 않았어, 바보야!
You told the police that I use drugs, you bastard!
내가 마약을 한다고 경찰에 신고했잖아 , 이 새끼야!
Did you go crazy or smell glue?
미쳤거나 접착제 냄새가 났나요?
I didn't tell on shit!
난 아무 말도 안 했어!
Yeah, I went crazy, broke in!
그래, 나 미쳤어, 침입했어!
If it weren't for my lawyer,
내 변호사가 아니었다면,
I would have fucked myself today, asshole!
오늘은 엿먹일 뻔 했어, 개자식아!
Gicheul,
기철,
fix this bastard!
이 놈을 고쳐라!
Everyone leave except Jungbae.
정배 빼고 다 떠나요.
Get out!
나가세요!
Now that we're alone,
이제 우리 둘만 남았으니,
tell me the truth.
나에게 진실을 말해.
Didn't think it was strange when they released Kwon Seungho,
권승호를 내보냈을 때 이상하게 생각하지 않았는데 ,
But do you find it strange when they let me go?
하지만 그들이 나를 놓아주었을 때 이상하다고 생각하시나요?
I did not say anything.
나는 아무 말 안했어.
And why did they release you?
그리고 그들은 왜 당신을 석방했습니까?
Seriously, Gicheul, it's done.
진짜로, 기철아, 끝났어.
You know I never lied to you.
내가 당신에게 거짓말을 한 적이 없다는 걸 당신도 알잖아요.
He is sure?
그 사람이 확실해요?
Gicheul.
기철.
It's a second accounting book for the nightclub.
나이트클럽의 두 번째 회계장부입니다.
Explain.
설명하다.
-Jungbae. -Say.
-정배. -말하다.
Were you pocketing money?
돈을 훔치고 있었나요?
Did you look for my information?
내 정보를 찾아보셨나요?
Did you really think...
정말 생각한 걸까요...
that I wouldn't find out that you're selling my stuff?
당신이 내 물건을 파는 걸 내가 알 수 없을 거라고요 ?
Your things?
당신의 물건?
Our things.
우리 물건.
What?
무엇?
When the drug runs out, addicts turn away.
약이 다 떨어지면 중독자들은 등을 돌린다.
I only stocked up a little as a precaution.
예방 차원에서 소량만 비축해 두었습니다.
You should have told me.
나한테 말했어야 했는데.
As if you would agree if I had spoken.
내가 말을 했다면 당신도 동의할 것처럼요 .
Was it for that reason?
그런 이유였나요?
Then bring what you missed.
그런 다음 놓친 것을 가져 오십시오.
Bring it to me.
나에게 가져 와봐.
Did you think I wouldn't know you were pocketing it?
당신 이 그것을 주머니에 넣고 있다는 것을 내가 모를 거라고 생각했나요 ?
Take all your money. Go to some very distant interior.
돈을 모두 가져가세요. 아주 먼 내부로 가십시오.
And stay away from the police.
그리고 경찰을 멀리하세요.
Why?
왜?
Can't I want to make money too?
나도 돈 벌면 안 될까 ?
I also have ambitions.
나에게도 야망이 있다.
Why can't I be successful like you?
나는 왜 당신처럼 성공하지 못하는 걸까요?
You can do whatever you want,
당신이 원하는 것은 무엇이든 할 수 있습니다.
But you can't lie to me.
하지만 당신은 나에게 거짓말을 할 수 없습니다.
I understood.
나는 이해했다.
Serious? After 20 years?
심각한? 20년 후?
Are you going to kick me out for this?
이것 때문에 나를 쫓아낼 건가요?
It's me you need by your side now.
지금 당신 옆에 필요한 사람은 바로 나입니다 .
Gicheul...
기철...
Your perception is distorted. It's Yu Euijeong's fault, the disgusting police officer!
당신의 인식은 왜곡되어 있습니다. 역겨운 경찰 유의정 탓이다!
I am wrong?
내가 틀렸어?
Come to mouth.
입으로 오세요.
Otherwise I'll kill you.
그렇지 않으면 내가 당신을 죽일 것입니다.
I don't hang around cops. Different from you!
나는 경찰들과 어울리지 않습니다. 너랑은 달라!
And she still insists on Kwon Seungho just because he's close to her!
그리고 그녀는 여전히 권승호가 자신과 가깝다는 이유만으로 고집을 부리고 있다!
There are strange things happening here,
여기서 이상한 일이 일어나고 있습니다.
but you never suspected him!
하지만 당신은 그를 의심한 적이 없어요!
I'm not the one who should be expelled!
나는 추방되어야 할 사람이 아니다!
It's Yu Euijeong and Kwon Seungho!
유의정과 권승호입니다!
One day, you will realize that you were blind.
어느 날 당신은 자신이 장님이었다는 것을 깨닫게 될 것입니다.
I guarantee.
나는 보장한다.
Look into my eyes.
내 눈을 들여다.
You're thinking about a lot of things, right?
많은 생각을 하고 계시죠?
Go in peace, sir.
평안히 가세요, 선생님.
You look good in that suit.
그 옷이 잘 어울리네요.
Let's go in and take care of the boss.
들어가서 보스를 처리하자.
Where are you going?
어디 가세요?
He said we needed to move forward or expel someone.
그는 우리가 앞으로 나아가 거나 누군가를 추방해야 한다고 말했습니다.
Got it, sir.
알겠습니다.
Who is it?
누구입니까?
It's Kwon Seungho.
권승호입니다.
In between.
사이.
Boss.
사장.
Must be upset
당황스러워야 해
because of Jungbae.
정배 때문에.
I know how you feel, but shouldn't we go back...
네 기분은 알지만, 돌아가면 안 될까...
the negotiations from before?
이전 협상?
I need to remain firm.
나는 굳건함을 유지해야합니다.
Yes sir.
알겠습니다.
Answer.
답변.
Hello? Kwon Seungho speaking.
안녕하세요? 말하는 권승호.
Hi, it's Haeryun.
안녕하세요, 해륜이에요.
Oi, Haeryun.
Oi, Haeryun.
You are with Mr. Jung, right?
정 선생님이랑 같이 계시죠?
I am.
그래요.
I was about to call you.
너한테 전화하려고 했어.
I thought we'd get together
난 우리가 같이 모일 거라고 생각했는데
to clear everything up and talk about future plans.
모든 것을 정리 하고 향후 계획에 대해 이야기합니다.
How can we think about the future?
우리는 미래에 대해 어떻게 생각할 수 있습니까?
with such an uncertain gift?
그렇게 불확실한 선물을 가지고?
All this confusion started from here. My apologies.
이 모든 혼란은 여기서부터 시작됐다. 사과드립니다.
Aren’t others usually the ones apologizing on your behalf?
대신 사과하는 사람은 보통 다른 사람이 아닌가요 ?
If I have time left,
시간이 남으면,
I will personally accept Seungho's apology.
저는 승호씨의 사과를 개인적으로 받아들이겠습니다 .
Could it be?
그럴 수 있을까?
Just schedule the time.
시간만 정하면 됩니다.
Wouldn't that be nice, Seungho?
좋지 않니, 승호?
Clear. Just tell me the time, and I'll be there.
분명한. 시간만 알려주시면 제가 거기로 갈게요.
I'll call again later.
나중에 다시 전화할게요.
Let's go out together.
같이 나가자.
What does she want?
그녀는 무엇을 원합니까?
Whatever it is, it's positive for us.
그것이 무엇이든 그것은 우리에게 긍정적입니다.
Lee Haeryun is giving us an opportunity.
이해련이 우리에게 기회를 주고 있다 .
Boss,
사장,
I will do whatever it takes
난 무슨 일이든 할 거야
to make her change her mind.
그녀의 마음을 바꾸게 만들기 위해.
I promise
약속해요
that I won't disappoint you.
내가 당신을 실망시키지 않을 거라는 걸요.
Right.
오른쪽.
I also don't want any more disappointments.
나 역시 더 이상의 실망을 원하지 않는다.
You seem happy.
너 행복해 보여.
Can I at least leave in peace?
적어도 평화롭게 떠날 수 있을까요?
Hey, chubby.
안녕, 통통한.
You always take the easy way out.
당신은 항상 쉬운 길을 택합니다.
That's why he gained so much weight.
그 때문에 그는 살이 많이 쪘다.
Go down the stairs.
계단을 내려 가다.
Oh no! The elevator broke.
안 돼! 엘리베이터가 고장났습니다.
Holy shit, you piece of shit!
이런 젠장, 이 빌어먹을 놈아!
Son of a bitch!
개자식!
Fucking asshole!
빌어먹을 새끼!
Boss Seo, wait!
서 사장님, 잠깐만요!
Shit!
똥!
You needed a good spanking
당신은 좋은 때리기가 필요했습니다
to never think about coming back here again, you piece of shit.
다시는 여기로 돌아올 생각을 하지 말라는 거야 , 이 빌어먹을 놈아.
Listen.
듣다.
Never set foot in this neighborhood again.
다시는 이 동네에 발을 들여놓지 마세요.
Son of a bitch!
개자식!
Hey.
여기요.
What is in the church today?
오늘날 교회에는 무엇이 있습니까?
How about going in alone? I stay here waiting.
혼자 들어가는 게 어때요? 나는 여기서 기다리고 있다.
It's not good to see us together, right?
우리 같이 보는 건 좋지 않죠?
What is happening?
무슨 일이 일어나고 있나요?
She was very quick in the kitchen.
그녀는 부엌에서 매우 빨랐습니다.
He got the reputation of being an incredible person.
그는 놀라운 사람이라는 평판을 얻었습니다.
When they suggested creating a petition
청원서 작성을 제안했을 때
to bar the institution for people with disabilities,
장애인 시설을 금지하기 위해 ,
Theresa didn't mince words.
테레사는 말을 잘 하지 않았다.
And truth.
그리고 진실.
Whenever she saw a child, she would give them a pencil as a gift.
그녀는 아이를 볼 때마다 연필을 선물로 주곤 했습니다.
She had this sweet way.
그녀는 이런 좋은 방법을 가졌습니다.
The Theresa Hwang Jinsook I knew
내가 아는 테레사 황진숙
shone like a jewel,
보석처럼 빛났고,
but he always gave room for others to shine.
그러나 그는 항상 다른 사람들이 빛날 수 있는 여지를 주었습니다.
And where is dear Theresa now?
그런데 사랑하는 테레사는 지금 어디에 있나요?
In everyone's memory.
모두의 기억 속에.
Her daughter is here today.
오늘은 그녀의 딸이 여기에 있습니다.
Then, take a moment to talk to her.
그런 다음 잠시 시간을 내어 그녀와 이야기를 나눠보세요.
Share memories of Theresa with her.
테레사의 추억을 그녀와 공유하세요.
That way, she will live forever.
그렇게 하면 그녀는 영원히 살 수 있을 것이다.
We ask that you pour out your mercy
우리는 당신의 자비를 부어 주시기를 간구합니다
about those who mourn the loss of their loved ones.
사랑하는 사람을 잃은 슬픔에 빠진 사람들에 대해 .
Surround them with your love and compassion
당신의 사랑과 연민으로 그들을 둘러싸십시오.
and wipes your tears.
그리고 눈물을 닦아주세요.
As believers in your life and resurrection,
당신의 삶과 부활을 믿는 신자로서,
we affirm that death is not the end,
우리는 죽음이 끝이 아니라는 것을 확신합니다.
but the beginning of a new and eternal existence.
그러나 새롭고 영원한 존재의 시작입니다 .
They didn't need to have done that.
그들은 그렇게 할 필요가 없었습니다.
Of course we needed it.
물론 우리는 그것이 필요했습니다.
We have attended church together for over 20 years.
우리는 20년 넘게 함께 교회를 다녔습니다 .
How is your older brother?
형은 잘 지내요?
He and my son Changdae said they were going to the library,
아들 창대랑 도서관에 간다고 해서,
but they would always get ready.
하지만 그들은 언제나 준비가 되어 있었습니다.
He is fine.
그는 괜찮습니다.
You haven't changed a bit. She looks like the same young woman as always.
당신은 조금도 변하지 않았습니다. 그녀는 언제나와 같은 젊은 여성처럼 보입니다.
I was sad that I couldn't go to her funeral.
나는 그녀의 장례식에 갈 수 없어서 슬펐다 .
But Gicheul asked us
그런데 기철이가 우리에게 물었어요.
that we organized this.
우리가 이것을 조직했다고요.
Thank you, ma'am.
감사합니다 사모님.
You haven't changed a bit. She looks like the same young woman as always.
당신은 조금도 변하지 않았습니다. 그녀는 언제나와 같은 젊은 여성처럼 보입니다.
How is your older brother?
형은 잘 지내요?
He and my son Changdae said they were going to the library,
아들 창대랑 도서관에 간다고 해서,
but they would always get ready.
하지만 그들은 언제나 준비가 되어 있었습니다.
He is fine.
그는 괜찮습니다.
Hello?
안녕하세요?
It's Jung Gicheul speaking.
정기철입니다.
Hello, Mr. Jung.
안녕하세요, 정 선생님.
What did Jungbae want to know?
정배가 알고 싶었던 것은 무엇일까?
If Yu Euijeong lived in Wonju,
유의정이 원주에 살았다면
if he studied at the same school as Kwon Seungho
권승호랑 같은 학교 다녔다면
and whether they were neighbors.
그리고 그들이 이웃인지 여부.
I want you to discover this.
나는 당신이 이것을 발견하기를 바랍니다.
Now?
지금?
I don't think she ever moved to Wonju and always lived in Seoul.
내 생각에 그녀는 원주로 이사한 적도 없고 항상 서울에서 살았다.
Sim, Sr. Jung.
심 선생님 정.
Thanks.
감사해요.
Euijeong.
의정.
Let's stay another hour.
한 시간 더 머물자.
Why?
왜?
I want to be at peace...
평화롭게 있고 싶다...
admiring your face for an hour.
한 시간 동안 당신의 얼굴을 감상했습니다.
Captain Seok called.
석 선장이 전화했다.
He said they are in a cafe.
그는 그들이 카페에 있다고 말했습니다.
And where were they before?
그리고 그들은 전에 어디에 있었나요?
He mentioned a church, but I'm not sure.
그는 교회에 대해 언급했지만 확실하지는 않습니다.
-Hello? -Hello, sir. It is me.
-안녕하세요? -안녕하세요 선생님. 나야.
Oh, Sr. Lee.
아, 이 선생님.
That detective Cheon came here.
그 천 형사가 여기 왔어요.
He asked me to check
나한테 확인해 보라고 하더군요
whether retired police officer Yu Dukhoon worked in Gangwon.
유덕훈 퇴직경찰관이 강원도에서 근무했는지.
When I said I couldn't,
내가 할 수 없다고 말했을 때,
He said he would find out at the Retired Police Officers Association.
그는 은퇴경찰협회에서 알아보겠다고 말했다 .
Will Gicheul take Euijeong hostage...
기철은 의정을 인질로 잡을 것인가 ..
PRESS
누르다
I'm writing an essay about former police officer Yu Dukhoon.
전직 경찰관 유덕훈에 대한 에세이를 쓰고 있습니다 .
I need a lot of information.
많은 정보가 필요합니다.
RETIRED POLICE OFFICERS ASSOCIATION
퇴직경찰협회
My workday will end.
나의 근무일은 끝날 것이다.
Is it urgent?
긴급한 일인가요?
I understand. You need to go home, right?
이해합니다. 집에 가야 해, 그렇지?
By the way, it seems...
그건 그렇고...
that he was never...
그 사람은 절대 아니었다고...
in Gangwon Province.
강원도에서.
It's a great discovery.
대단한 발견이네요.
Hello.
안녕하세요.
Is your name Cheon Jinpyung by any chance?
혹시 이름이 천진평인가요?
It is me.
나야.
You know me, right?
저 아시죠?
Mr. Jung sent me here.
정 선생님이 저를 여기로 보냈어요.
Can we talk for a moment?
잠시 얘기 좀 할 수 있을까요?
Clear.
분명한.
Why talk in the rain?
왜 빗속에서 이야기합니까?
By the way, what documents are these?
그런데, 이것은 무슨 서류입니까?
These? Why the question?
이것들? 질문이 왜요?
I'm just following orders from my boss.
나는 단지 상사의 명령을 따를 뿐입니다.
I'd better ask him.
그에게 물어보는 게 나을 것 같아요.
Do not wait.
기다리지 마.
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
I want to see the documents first.
서류를 먼저 보고 싶어요.
I already said there's nothing.
이미 아무것도 없다고 말했어요.
Drugs!
약제!
Holy crap!
이런 세상에!
What the hell is that? Give me these documents right away.
도대체 무슨 일이 있다는 것입니다? 이 서류를 당장 나에게 주세요.
Who are you, anyway?
어쨌든 당신은 누구입니까?
The order came from my boss!
사장님께서 주문을 주셨어요!
Give me those documents now!
지금 당장 그 서류를 주세요!
Not even fucking that came from him.
그 사람에게서 나온 빌어 먹을 것도 아닙니다.
This is bullshit. Listen.
이것은 헛소리입니다. 듣다.
What makes a police officer pretend to work for a criminal?
경찰관이 범죄자를 위해 일하는 것처럼 가장하는 이유는 무엇입니까?
Veteran police officer Park Junmo.
베테랑 경찰 박준모.
Genro do Yu Dukhoon.
겐로도 유덕훈.
What confusion are you creating?
당신은 어떤 혼란을 만들고 있습니까?
Cheon Jinpyung, if you continue to be a doormat for bandits,
천진평 계속 도적들의 앞잡이가 된다면
will end up in prison.
결국 감옥에 갇히게 됩니다.
I will protect you sir
제가 지켜드리겠습니다 선생님
if you cooperate with the police.
경찰에 협조한다면.
"Cooperar"?
"쿠퍼러"?
Of course I will cooperate. I'll go the fuck!
물론 협력하겠습니다. 난 갈 거야 젠장!
Son of a bitch!
개자식!
Cum!
정액!
Fuck!
못쓰게 만들다!
Help me.
도와주세요.
Get off of me.
나에게서 떨어져.
VETERAN POLICE PARK JUNMO
베테랑 경찰 박준모
Gicheul.
기철.
I must go now.
난 이제 가야한다.
See you. Thanks for today.
또 봐요. 오늘 고마워요.
The number you dialed...
당신이 걸었던 전화번호는...
Subtitles: Tharsis Nóbrega de Araújo
자막: Tharsis N??brega de Ara??jo